Guide to the New-York Historical Society Portrait Collection circa 1640-2020 (bulk, 1800-1950) PR 52
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Individuals and Family Groups, 59621
  - Subseries I.B. Individuals and Family Groups: Medium Format
    - Grim, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Grim, Elizabeth Daddy (Drawer Medium)
    - Grim, Philip (Drawer Medium)
    - Grimes, Bryan (Drawer Medium)
    - Grissenhainer, F. W. [Frederick William Gessenhainer?] (Drawer Medium)
    - Griswold, Rufus W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gros, Antoine Jean (Drawer Medium)
    - Grover, Cuvier (Drawer Medium)
    - Grundy, Felix (Drawer Medium)
    - Guernsey, R. S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Guitry, Sacha (Drawer Medium)
    - Gulick, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Gunther, Christian G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Gurney, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Guyer, Johann Jakob (Drawer Medium)
    - Gwin, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Gwinnett, Button (Drawer Medium)
    - Habershamp, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Hackett (Drawer Medium)
    - Haffen, Louis F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hahn, Michael (Drawer Medium)
    - Hahnemann, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Haid, Leo (Drawer Medium)
    - Haines, Thomas R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hale, Edward Everett (Drawer Medium)
    - Hale, John P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hale, Nathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Hall, Abraham Oakey (Drawer Medium)
    - Hall, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Hall, Lyman (Drawer Medium)
    - Hall, Nathan K. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hall, Norman J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hall, W. W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hall, Willard (Drawer Medium)
    - Halleck, Fitz-Greene (Drawer Medium)
    - Halleck, Henry Wager (Drawer Medium)
    - Hallett, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Hallgarten, Julius [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Hallock, William K. CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Hallowill, Morris L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamerton, Philip Gilbert (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamilton, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamilton, Alexander (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamilton, Alexander, Jr. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamilton, Charles M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamilton, Charles Smith (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamilton, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamlin, H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hamond, Andrew Snape (Drawer Medium)
    - Hampden, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hancock, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hancock, Winfield S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Handel, George Frederic (Drawer Medium)
    - Hanna, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Hansen, Cornelius (Drawer Medium)
    - Hanson, Alexander Contee (Drawer Medium)
    - Hanson, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hanson, Roger (Drawer Medium)
    - Harbord, James G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hardenbergh, James B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Harding, Warren G. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Hardt, Henry LeBaron CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Hardy, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Harkins, Matthew (Drawer Medium)
    - Harlan, John Marshall (Drawer Medium)
    - Harman, Jos. (Drawer Medium)
    - Harmon, Judson (Drawer Medium)
    - Harney, William Selby (Drawer Medium)
    - Harper, Arthur C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Harper, Fletcher (Drawer Medium)
    - Harpignies, Henri-Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Harris, Elijah P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Harris, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Harrison, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Harrison, Benjamin, President, and wife (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Harrison, Mary Lord (Drawer Medium)
    - Harrison, William Henry, and wife (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Hart, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hartley, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Hartranft, John F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hartsuff, George L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Harvey, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Haskell, D. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hassler, J. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hastings, Thomas S. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Havemeyer, William F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Haven, Mrs. Woodward (Drawer Medium)
    - Hawes, George Elias CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Hawes, Joel (Drawer Medium)
    - Hawes, Robert L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hawks, Francis L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hawkins, Rush C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hawley, Jos. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hawthorne, Nathaniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Haydn, Michael (Drawer Medium)
    - Hayes, Patrick J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hayes Rutherford B. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Hayes, Wade H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hayne, Isaac W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hayne, Robert Y. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hays, Harry T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hays, Jacob (Drawer Medium)
    - Hazard, Abigail Arthur (Drawer Medium)
    - Hazard, Ebenezer (Drawer Medium)
    - Hazlett, Capt. (Drawer Medium)
    - Healy, A. Augustus (Drawer Medium)
    - Heathcote, Caleb (Drawer Medium)
    - Heber, Reginald (Drawer Medium)
    - Heckscher, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Heckwelder, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hedden, Joseph Jr. (memorial) (Drawer Medium)
    - Hedges, Job Elmer (Drawer Medium)
    - Heem, Jan Davidsz de (Drawer Medium)
    - Heermann, Lewis (Drawer Medium)
    - Hegeman, John R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Heidegger, C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Heintzelman, Samuel P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Helm, Benjamin H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Helmholtz, Hermann von (Drawer Medium)
    - Helper, Hinton Rowan (Drawer Medium)
    - Hembel, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Hendricks, John A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hendricks, Thomas A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Henner, J. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hennessy, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hennessy, John Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Henry, P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Henry, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Henschel, Albert E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Henshaw, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Henshaw, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Henson, Josiah (Drawer Medium)
    - Herkomer, Hubert, and children (Drawer Medium)
    - Heron, Matilda (Drawer Medium)
    - Herrick, Charles P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Herschel, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Herron, F. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Heslin, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Heth, Harry (Drawer Medium)
    - Herter, Christine Archibald (Drawer Medium)
    - Hewitt, Abram S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hewlett, Samuel M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hickey, Jim (Drawer Medium)
    - Hicks, Elias (Drawer Medium)
    - Hicks, Thomas Holliday (Drawer Medium)
    - Hicks, Whitehead (Drawer Medium)
    - Hidden, Harry B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Higginson, Henry L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hill, Ambrose Powell (Drawer Medium)
    - Hill, Daniel Harvey (Drawer Medium)
    - Hill, George H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hill, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Hill, Nicholas (Drawer Medium)
    - Hillis, Newell Dwight (Drawer Medium)
    - Hillyer, W. S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Himes, Joshua V. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hindman, Thomas C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hinds, W. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hinks, Edward W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hiscox, E. T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hiscox, Freeman CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Hiscox, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Hitchcock, E. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoady, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoar, E. R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hobart, Frederick CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Hobart, Harrison (Drawer Medium)
    - Hobart, John Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Hobart, John Sloss (Drawer Medium)
    - Hobson, Richmond Pearson (Drawer Medium)
    - Hodges, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Hodgkinson, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoe, Richard M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoffman, Charles Fred (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoffman, Dean (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoffman, Eugene A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoffman, H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoffman, John T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoffman, Josiah Ogden (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoffman, Samuel Verplanck (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoffman, V. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hogarth, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoke, Robert F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Holbein, Hans (Drawer Medium)
    - Holcomb, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Holcombe, Wm. Frederic (Drawer Medium)
    - Holley, Sallie, and Putnam, Caroline F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (Drawer Medium)
    - Holmson, Mary Ann (Drawer Medium)
    - Holsman, Daniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Holstein, Otto (Drawer Medium)
    - Holt, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Homer, Louise (Drawer Medium)
    - Hondius, Abraham (Drawer Medium)
    - Honyman, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Hood, Samuel, Viscount (Drawer Medium)
    - Hooker, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Hooper, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoover, Herbert (Drawer Medium)
    - Hopkins, Ellen Dunlap (Drawer Medium)
    - Hopkins, Esek (Drawer Medium)
    - Hopkins, Samuel M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hopkins, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Hopper, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoppin, William Jones (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoppner, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Horton, J. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hosack, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Hostetler [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Houdon, Jean Antoine (Drawer Medium)
    - Hough, Franklin B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Houghton, Henry O. (Drawer Medium)
    - Houston, Sam (Drawer Medium)
    - Hovey, Alvin P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Howard, Harry (Drawer Medium)
    - Howard, John Eager (Drawer Medium)
    - Howard, Oliver O. (Drawer Medium)
    - Howard, William A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Howard, William G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Howe, F. T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Howe, Julia Ward (Drawer Medium)
    - Howe, S. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Howe, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Howells, William Dean (Drawer Medium)
    - Howland, Henry Elias (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoyt, Gabriel P. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoyt, John Sherman, Mrs., and children (Drawer Medium)
    - Hoze, Jean (Drawer Medium)
    - Hubbard, L. F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hubbard, N. T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Huger, Ben (Drawer Medium)
    - Hughes, C. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hughes, Charles E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hughes, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hugo, Victor (Drawer Medium)
    - Hull, Laurens (Drawer Medium)
    - Humboldt, Alexander von (Drawer Medium)
    - Humes, William B. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Humphrey, Hubert (Drawer Medium)
    - Humphreys, Andrew Atkinson (Drawer Medium)
    - Hunt, Henry Jackson (Drawer Medium)
    - Hunt, Henry Jackson and Duane, James C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hunt, Lee D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hunt, Nelson G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hunt, Peter (Drawer Medium)
    - Hunt, Ward (Drawer Medium)
    - Hunter, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Huntington, C. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Huntington, Jedediah (Drawer Medium)
    - Huntington, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Hurburt, Stephen Augustus (Drawer Medium)
    - Hurbut, Edwin (Drawer Medium)
    - Hurlburt, W. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hurst, John F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Hus, Jan (Drawer Medium)
    - Hutcheson, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Hutchings, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hutchinson, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Hyatt, Stephen Burdett CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Hyde, James H. w/Hyde, Henry H. (Drawer Medium)
      James Hazen Hyde and Henry B. Hyde removed, 12/2019. Placed with Hyde papers.
    - Hyer, Tom (Drawer Medium)
    - Imboden, John David (Drawer Medium)
    - Impellitteri, Vincent R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ingalls, Rufus (Drawer Medium)
    - Ingersoll, Jared (Drawer Medium)
    - Ingersoll, Robert J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Inglis, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Inglis, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Ingram, Marshall (Drawer Medium)
    - Ingres, Jean Auguste Dominique (Drawer Medium)
    - Inness, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Iredell, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Irving, Washington (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Iselin, Dorothy (Drawer Medium)
    - Iselin, Fanny Garner (Drawer Medium)
    - Iverson, Alfred (Drawer Medium)
    - Izard, Alice De Lancey (Drawer Medium)
    - Izard, Ralph (Drawer Medium)
    - Jackson, Andrew (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Jackson, Howell E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Jackson, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Jackson, Joseph Devonsher (Drawer Medium)
    - Jackson, T. J. "Stonewall" (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Jackson, W. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Jacobi, Abraham [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - James, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - James, Josiah CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - James, Willis [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Jameson, Charles Davis (Drawer Medium)
    - Janssens, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Jaquess, James F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Jauncey, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Jay (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Jay, John
      Jay, William
    - Jefferson, Thomas (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Jerome (Drawer Medium)
    - Jerome, A. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Jesup, Morris Ketchum [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Joan of Arc, Saint (Drawer Medium)
    - Johnson (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Johnson, Andrew (separate folder)
      Johnson, Ben
      Johnson, Edward
      Johnson, Evan M.
      Johnson, G. H. M.
      Johnson, Herschel
      Johnson, Lyndon Baines
      Johnson, Richard Mento
      Johnson, Rossiter
      Johnson, William (1771-1834)
      Johnson, William, Sir (1715-1774)
      Johnson, William Ransom
      Johnson, William Samuel
    - Johnston, Albert Sidney (Drawer Medium)
    - Johnston, D. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Johnston, Harriet Lane (Drawer Medium)
    - Johnston, Joseph Eggleston (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Johnston, William F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Jones (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Jones, Absalom
      Jones, Benjamin S. and Elizabeth
      Jones, Charles C. Jr.
      Jones, David M.
      Jones, David R.
      Jones, Harrison, Mrs.
      Jones, Inigo
      Jones, James A.
      Jones, James H.
      Jones, John M.
      Jones, John Paul (separate folder)
      Jones, Owen
      Jones, Patrick H.
      Jones, Samuel
      Jones, Singleton T.
      Jones, William E.
    - Jordan, Thomas J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Josephine, Empress (Drawer Medium)
    - Judson, Adoniram (Drawer Medium)
    - Jumel, Eliza Bowen (Drawer Medium)
    - Junger, Aegidius (Drawer Medium)
    - Kain, John J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kane, Elisha Kent (Drawer Medium)
    - Kane, George P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kane, Thomas Leiper (Drawer Medium)
    - Kauffman, Theodor (Drawer Medium)
    - Kautz, August Valentine (Drawer Medium)
    - Kawabe (Drawer Medium)
    - Kearney, John F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kearny, Philip (Drawer Medium)
    - Kearny, Stephen Watts (Drawer Medium)
    - Keene, Thomas W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Keese, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Keith, Charles Clarence Tracy CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Keith, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Kelby, Robert H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kelley, William Darrah (Drawer Medium)
    - Kellogg, William P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kelly, Eugene [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Kelly, Fitzroy (Drawer Medium)
    - Kelly, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Kemble, Fanny (Drawer Medium)
    - Kemble, Gouverneur (Drawer Medium)
    - Kemble, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Kenan, Georgia (Drawer Medium)
    - Kendall, Amos (Drawer Medium)
    - Kendall, William Sergeant (Drawer Medium)
    - Kendrick, H. L. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Kennedy (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Kennedy, Anne Watts
      Kennedy, Archibald
      Kennedy, Edward, and wife
      Kennedy, John A.
      Kennedy, John P.
      Kennedy, Robert Lenox [crossed out]
    - Kennington, Thomas Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Kent, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Ketchum, Alexander Phoenix CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Ketchum, Edgar Jr. CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Key, Francis Scott (Drawer Medium)
    - Kilpatrick, Hugh Judson (Drawer Medium)
    - Kimball, Leroy (Drawer Medium)
    - Kimball, Nathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Kimball, Richard B. (Drawer Medium)
    - King (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      King, Billie Jean (photo by Lynn Gilbert is in Photographer's File, PR 50)
      King, Charles
      King, James Gordon
      King, John A.
      King, Jonas
      King, Preston
      King, Richard [crossed out]
      King, Rufus (1755-1827)
      King, Rufus (1814-1876)
      King, Thomas
      King, W. R.
    - Kinlock, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Kinney, Benjamin West (tombstone) (Drawer Medium)
    - Kinsey, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Kipling, Rudyard (Drawer Medium)
    - Kirk, E. N. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kirkland, William W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kirkwood, Samuel Jordan (Drawer Medium)
    - Kittredge, Charles W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kleber, Jean-Baptiste (Drawer Medium)
    - Knapp, Jacob (Drawer Medium)
    - Knapp, Joseph F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Knecht, Marcel (Drawer Medium)
    - Knopf, S. Adolphus (Drawer Medium)
    - Knox, E. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Knowles, I. S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Knowlton, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Koch, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Kosciuszko, Thaddeus (Drawer Medium)
    - Kohler, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Kossuth, Louis (Drawer Medium)
    - Krehbiel, Henry Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Kreischer, N. (Drawer Medium)
    - Kunze, John Christopher (Drawer Medium)
    - Kuypers, Gerardus A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Laemmle, Carl (Drawer Medium)
    - Lafayette, Marquis de (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Lagow (Drawer Medium)
    - LaGrange, Madame (Drawer Medium)
    - Laidlie, Archibald (Drawer Medium)
    - Laidlie, Mary (Drawer Medium)
    - Lambdin, George Cochran (Drawer Medium)
    - Lambdin, James Reid (Drawer Medium)
    - Lamont, Daniel S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lander, Frederick West (Drawer Medium)
    - Landon, Alfred Mossman (Drawer Medium)
    - Landor, Walter Savage (Drawer Medium)
    - Lane, James H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lane, John W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lane, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Lanfranco, Giovanni (Drawer Medium)
    - Lang, Andrew (Drawer Medium)
    - Lanman, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Lansing, D. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lansing, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Lardner, Lynford (Drawer Medium)
    - La Rochefoucauld, Francois, duc de (Drawer Medium)
    - Lathrop, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Lauman, Jacob Gartner (Drawer Medium)
    - Laurence, Abbott (Drawer Medium)
    - Laurence, William Beach (Drawer Medium)
    - Laurens, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Laurens, J. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Laurens, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Lauterbach, Edward [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Law, Evander MacIver (Drawer Medium)
    - Law, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Law, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Lawrence, Augustine Hicks (Drawer Medium)
    - Lawrence, Katherine Luquer (Drawer Medium)
    - Lawrence, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Lawrence, William Van Duzer (Drawer Medium)
    - Lawrie, Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - Lawson, Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - Lay, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Leale, Charles Augustus (Drawer Medium)
    - Leasure, Daniel (Drawer Medium)
    - LeBrun, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Lee (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Lee, Fitzhugh
      Lee, Francis Lightfoot
      Lee, Gideon
      Lee, Henry
      Lee, Josh
      Lee, Richard Henry
      Lee, Robert E. (separate folder)
      Lee, William Henry Fitzhugh
    - Lefferts, Charles MacKubin (Drawer Medium)
    - Lefferts, Marshall (Drawer Medium)
    - Leggett, Mortimer Dormer (Drawer Medium)
    - Leib, Michael (Drawer Medium)
    - Leipziger, Henry M. (Drawer Medium)
    - LeMire, Aubert (Drawer Medium)
    - Leney, William S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lenox, James [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Lentze, E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lemondant, Jean Julien (Drawer Medium)
    - LeRoy, W. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Leo XIII, Pope (Drawer Medium)
    - Leonard, Robert W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Leonardo da Vinci (Drawer Medium)
    - Leslie, Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - Lessore, Henri (Drawer Medium)
    - Lessore, Mrs. Henri (Drawer Medium)
    - Leventhorpe, Collett (Drawer Medium)
    - Levin, Mrs. Harold (Drawer Medium)
    - Levin, Harold L., and family (Drawer Medium)
    - Levy, Moses (Drawer Medium)
    - Levy, Samson (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, Edmund D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, Frederick Christian (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, John Frederick (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, Joseph Horace (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, Mordecai (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, Morgan (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, William Gaston (Drawer Medium)
    - Lewis, William Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Lexow, Clarence (Drawer Medium)
    - Leypoldt, Frederick (Drawer Medium)
    - Lhermitte, L. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - L'Hommedieu, Ezra (Drawer Medium)
    - Liddell, St John R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Liebermann, Max (Drawer Medium)
    - Lincoln, Abraham (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Allegorical with Washington
      Allegorical with emancipation themes
      Bearded
      ....Bust-Length (3 folders)
      ....Half-Length
      ....¾ and Full Length
      Beardless (2 folders)
      Memorial Broadsides on paper
      Memorial Broadsides on cloth
      Photomechanical reproductions
      ....Death-Bed scenes
      ....Inaugurations
      ....Assassination
      ....Lying in state and funeral
      Statues and Monuments (2 folders)
      With staff and generals
    - Lincoln, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Lincoln, Mary Todd (Drawer Medium)
    - Lincoln, Robert [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Lindbergh, Charles A., and family (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Lindley, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Lindsay, John V. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lingard, Alice Dunning (Drawer Medium)
    - Linn, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Lippard, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Liszt, Franz (Drawer Medium)
    - Litta, Marie (Drawer Medium)
    - Little, J. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Livingston (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Livingston, Carroll
      Livingston, Edward
      Livingston, Brockholst
      Livingston, John
      Livingston, Philip
      Livingston, William
    - Livingstone, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Lloyd, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Lockwood, Henry Hayes (Drawer Medium)
    - Loew, Marcus (Drawer Medium)
    - Logan, John A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth (separate folder) [see also Charles Sumner] (Drawer Medium)
    - Longstreet, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Longstreth, Morris (Drawer Medium)
    - Lossing, Benson J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Loutherbourg, Philippe-Jacques de (Drawer Medium)
    - Loughlin, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Lovelace, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Loveridge, Henry CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Low (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Low, Abbot Augustus [crossed out]
      Low, Abiel Abbot, and family
      Low, Nicholas W.
      Low, Seth
      Low, Will H.
    - Lowell, Abbott (Drawer Medium)
    - Lowell, James Russell (Drawer Medium)
    - Luckey, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Ludden, Patrick Anthony (Drawer Medium)
    - Ludlow, Edmund (Drawer Medium)
    - Ludlow, H. G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lyautey, Marechal (Drawer Medium)
    - Lydenberg, Harry M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Lydig, Rita d'Acosta (Drawer Medium)
    - Lyell, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Lyman, Theodore Benedict [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Lyon, Nathaniel (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Lynch, Dominick (Drawer Medium)
    - MacAlister, C. (Drawer Medium)
    - McAlpin, Edwin A. (Drawer Medium)
    - MacArthur, Douglas (Drawer Medium)
    - McCall, Edward Everett (Drawer Medium)
    - McCarter, Thomas N. (Drawer Medium)
    - McCausland, John (Drawer Medium)
    - McClintock, John (Drawer Medium)
    - McCloskey, William G. (Drawer Medium)
    - McComb, Eleazer M. (Drawer Medium)
    - McCown, John Porter (Drawer Medium)
    - McClellan, George B. (1826-1885) and wife (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - McClellan, George B. (1865-1940) (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - McClurg, Trevor (Drawer Medium)
    - McCulloch, Ben (Drawer Medium)
    - McCurr, John H. (Drawer Medium)
    - McDaniel, H. D. (Drawer Medium)
    - MacDonald, Pirie (Drawer Medium)
    - MacDonough, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - McDougall, Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - McDowell, Irvin (Drawer Medium)
    - McGee, James [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - McGilvery, Freeman (Drawer Medium)
    - MacGovern, George (Drawer Medium)